{
    "Student ID: 202": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What color did the sky turn from before it became blue?",
            "correct_answer": "Majestic orange"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What does the soft touch of orange bring to the author?",
            "correct_answer": "Happiness"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "In the text, what are the cars described as doing?",
            "correct_answer": "Sleekly racing with a pair of red lights"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "How does the author describe the city when the sky turns dark?",
            "correct_answer": "Small and dark, with just small bulbs and street lights"
        }
    ],
    "Student ID: 306": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What does the author see in the morning?",
            "correct_answer": "The sun clinging to the clouds"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What does the dark sky make the author feel?",
            "correct_answer": "Suffocate"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What compensates for the sunlight when the sky turns dark?",
            "correct_answer": "Small bulbs and street lights"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What does the author look forward to in the morning?",
            "correct_answer": "The orange coming back with all the shades"
        }
    ],
    "Student ID: 409": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What color does the sky turn to at the end of the text?",
            "correct_answer": "Blue"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What does the author do in peace?",
            "correct_answer": "Sleep"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the author\u2019s reaction to the dark sky?",
            "correct_answer": "It makes the author suffocate"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What does the author say the dark sky has to do?",
            "correct_answer": "Live by the whole night"
        }
    ],
    "Student ID: 5": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What does the author see in the morning?",
            "correct_answer": "The sun clinging to the clouds"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What does the author feel when the sky turns dark?",
            "correct_answer": "Suffocate"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What does the author look forward to in the morning?",
            "correct_answer": "The orange coming back with all the shades"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What does the author describe the city as when the sky turns dark?",
            "correct_answer": "Small and dark, with just small bulbs and street lights"
        }
    ]
}